hi everyone and welcome to new every day
みなさんこんにちは 、 毎日新しいものへ ようこそ
my name is Kari my name is Jen and do
私の名前は Kariです私の 名前はJenとdoです
you have an area in your life that needs
あなたの 人生に必要な 領域 があります
some fixing like maybe you find yourself
多分あなたは自分自身を見つけるようないくつかの固定
misunderstood all the time or maybe you
いつも誤解していた
misunderstand people well on today's
今日の人々をよく誤解する
show we're going to talk about that so
それ について 話す つもりであることを 示す
stay tuned this is new every day with
これをお楽しみにすることで 、毎日新しいです
Jen wagger and Carey web
Jen wagger と Carey web
[Music]
[音楽]
hi everyone thanks so much for tuning
こんにちは皆さん、チューニングに 感謝 します。
back into new every day and if this is
毎日 新しいものに戻り、これが
your first time tuning in thank you so
最初にチューニングしてくれてありがとうございます
much Jen and I have been doing this for
多くのJenと私はこれをやっている
almost three years
ほぼ 3年
yeah Wow it's been it's gone by really
ええ、 それは本当に行っているされている
quickly and we just sit and we talk
すぐに 座っ て 話す
about the Bible we talk about God we
聖書について私たちは神について話します
talk about life we talk about questions
私たちが質問について話す人生について話す
that we have or life situations that
私たちが持っているものや人生の状況
we've encountered that we want to share
我々は共有したいと思った
with you and honestly we learn so much
正直なところ、私たちはあまりにも多くを学ぶ
doing this and really benefit from it so
これを行うと、実際に それ の恩恵を受ける
thanks for tuning in and and we just
チューニングのための感謝と、 私たちだけ
sure welcome you mm-hmm
確かにあなたを歓迎するmm  -  hmm
this is your first time well we do
これは初めてのことです
welcome you thank you so much for tuning
チューニングに 感謝してい ます。
in and on today's show we ask the
で、 今日のショーに 私たちは尋ねます
question like have you ever been
あなたが今までに行ったような質問
misunderstood or or have you
誤解されたり、
misunderstood someone
誰かを誤解した
I mean communication is so important and
私は コミュニケーションがとても重要であること を意味し ます。
so often people just say things and then
それほど 頻繁に 人々は ちょうど その ことを言うと、
they wonder why they have been
彼らは なぜ 彼らが
misunderstood yeah or they text
誤解されたり、テキストが誤解されたりする
something and wonder why they you know
何か、彼らがなぜあなたが知っているのだろうか
they didn't pick up on things and oh
彼らは物事を拾わなかったし、 ああ
before the world of emoticons it was
顔文字の世界の前には
like what do you really mean what do you
あなたは何を本当に 意味して いるのですか？
really mean and so one of the things
本当に 意味がある ので、物事の一つ
that we've started actually in our house
私たちが実際に 家で始めたこと
because Kari and I share space together
カリと私は一緒に空間を共有する ため、
and basically were like hey we both need
そして基本的には ちょっと我々 の両方が必要 のようでした
a place to live why don't we you know
なぜ あなたは知って いないの ですか？
rent an apartment and share space and
アパートを借りてスペースを共有し、
one of the things that we've had to do
私たちが しなけれ ばならなかっ たことの一つ
is figure out how to understand each
それぞれを理解する方法を 見つけ出す れます
other communicate because I have a very
私は非常に
different communication skill and I like
異なるコミュニケーションスキルと私は好きです
to think she knows what I'm thinking or
彼女は私が考えていることを知っていると思うしたり、
feeling but I actually haven't said
私は実際には言っていない
anything and so you will often just say
何かとあなたはしばしばちょうど言うでしょう
just tell me and in my mind I'm like
ただ私に教えて、私の心の中で私は好きです
what can't you just can't I just infer
あなただけの私は 何を 推測することはできませんすることはできません
something and you're going to pick it up
あなたは それを拾う つもりです
so but it's so challenging and I think
だからそれはとても挑戦的 だと思う
that goes both ways yes like in in so
それは両方の 方法にはい
many relationships I think like how
私はどのように考えている多くの関係
could they not see that or how could he
彼らはそれを見ることができないか、彼はどのように
not know that that that's what I wanted
それが 私が望んでいたことを 知らない
him to do yes yes so often unless it
彼はそうしないと頻繁にそうする
comes right out and says it it's the
すぐに出てき て、 それが
person
人
then it's just miscommunicated so one
それはちょうどそのように誤解されている
example is so when you share space with
あなたとスペースを共有 するときの例です
someone like a kitchen you in my mind I
私の心の中のキッチンのような人
would like to put things in a certain
一定で物事を入れたいです
place and Kari and her mind would like
場所と カリー と彼女の心が欲しい
to anyway that was funny
とにかく面白かった
Kari likes to but we don't really know
カリは好きだ けど、私たちは本当に知りません
and so I always have a very specific
私はいつも非常に特異的です
spot for things and I don't always know
私はいつも知りません
it but I should know it because they end
それが終わるので私はそれを知るべきです
up there all the time like the tongs or
トングのようにすべての時間がアップしたり
Tupperware and they go one day we have
タッパーウェアと彼らは私たちがある日に行く
mix our measuring cups and I always put
私たちの測定カップ を混ぜて、私は いつも置く
them in the top drawer because that's
トップ引き出しの中にそれらそれだから
where the baking stuff goes in my mind
ベーキングのものは私の心の中に入ります
and Kari kept putting them in the second
そしてKariは2番目にそれらを入れ続けた
drawer and I'm thinking does she not
引き出しと私は彼女がないと思っている
know that they go in the top drawer but
彼らは上の引き出しに行く ことを知っている が、
it just strophe Bunker's because every
それは単にバンカーの ストーリー
time I'd go to close the top drawer the
一番上の引き出しを閉じて
baking cup would hit the top with the
ベーキングカップは
drawer thing yes and so I kept moving in
引き出し物はい、そう私は移動し続けた
this is the conversation would you like
これはあなた が 望む会話です
the mixing the measuring cups in the
計量カップを
second drawer and you said yes because
二番目の引き出しとあなたはそう言っ た
because the thing keeps hitting the
物事が
thing I said okay I can put the mixing
私が言った事は大丈夫です。
the measuring cups in the second drawer
第2引出しの計量カップ
as long as I know that's where they're
私が知っている限り、彼らはどこにいるの？
always going to end up because in my
いつも私の中で終わるつもりです
mind I want things at least there in one
心 私は、少なくとも そこ 1で 物事をしたいです
place I know where to go
私 はどこ に行くの か知っている場所
yeah and get them but that was we
ええ、それらを得るが、それは我々でした
thought the other person should just
他の人はちょうど
figure it out yeah without us actually
実際に私たちなしでそれを理解する
speaking yeah to each other and
ええ、お互いに話して
unfortunately that is one of the biggest
残念ながらそれ は最大のものの一つです
problems people often have is that we we
人々がよく抱く問題は、私たちは
have such this strong sense of needing
このような強い要望を持っている
to be accepted and belonging and
受け入れられ、所属すること
understood and understood that we think
理解し理解する
well they should know me they should
彼らは私に彼らを知るべきである
have no that's what I want but often we
私がしたいことはないが、しばしば
just want to be told so we're in the
私たちが
know yes right and oshare the mental
はいを正しく知っていて、精神をオシャレにする
framework I I I say that so much like in
フレームワークII 私は のように なるように多くを語ります
working in a dynamic environment it's I
ダイナミックな環境 で働いています
find it
それを見つける
so hard when people aren't sharing what
人々 が何を共有していないときはとても難しい
they're thinking so like a plan of care
彼らはケアの計画のように考えている
for you know in my case it's like a
あなたが私の場合に知っていることはようなものです
patient but if someone doesn't actually
しかし、もし誰かが実際に
articulate here's the problem here's the
ここではっきりとした問題 は
direction that we're gonna follow to get
我々が 取得 するつもり従っている方向
to a solution and here's we're gonna how
ソリューションへと、ここではどのように
we're gonna know that we've arrived yes
私達はイエスに到着したことを知ります
which is so important but it's hard to
それはとても重要ですが、それは難しいです
translate that into like like non work
それを 非仕事の ように変換する
relationships and still value those
それでも価値がある
communication tools that you would
あなたが望むコミュニケーションツール
actually employ at the workplace yes yes
実際に職場で雇用する はいはい
and what kerry said is so true that that
そして何 ケリーが言ったことは その ように真実であります
mental the mental model the schema yes
精神精神モデルスキーマはい
and so often I would say well I've been
そしてしばしば私はよく言いました。
thinking about this for two or three
これ について2〜3回考えている
weeks shoot I keep forgetting to
私は忘れています
communicate it yeah because in my mind I
私の心の 中 でそれを伝えなさい
want to have it all finished before I
私はそれをすべて前に終わらせたい
drop it on someone and so often huh I'll
誰かにそれをドロップし、しばしば私は
go into my wonderful administrative
私の素晴らしい行政に入る
assistant who is a planner and loves to
プランナー である とするのが大好きアシスタント
communicate about what's coming up and I
何が起きているのかを伝えて
have learned to start to say can I talk
私は話すことができると言うことを始めることを学んだ
to you about something I should have
私が持っているべきことについてあなたに
told you to listen oh and I'll try not
ああ 聞く ように言った と私はしないでください
to make eye contact but now we just
目の接触をするが、今私たちは ちょうど
laugh like yesterday she had this list
昨日のように 彼女 がこのリスト を 持っていた ように笑う
of 17 things and I said so and I
17のものの私は そう と 私は言った
literally turned away from her because I
文字通り彼女 から 離れた
knew what was yeah and you you have time
あなたは何だったのか分かっていました。あなたには時間があります。
to do this today is one more thing yeah
これを行うには、 今日はもう一つの事です
and we laugh because but that's part of
私たちは笑いますが、それは
the communication like now we laugh
今のようなコミュニケーションは笑う
about it when I come in two minutes
それについて私は 2分 で 来るとき
before I want something yeah and instead
私は何か欲しい前に代わりに
of saying beforehand can be look at
あらかじめ 言って おくこと が でき ます
doing this way that's why communication
このようにしているのは、コミュニケーションが
is so important that we that we say okay
私たちは 大丈夫と言う こと ほど重要です
what is coming up and for me it's really
何が来て いるのか 、私の ためには本当に
hard when I don't have all the details
私は すべての 詳細を 持って いないときは、ハード
to be sharing with someone cuz I don't
誰か と分かち合う
want them to start thinking about what
何を 考え始めてほしい
are the possible options when you know I
あなたが私を知っているときに可能なオプションです
arrived there yet yeah I haven't ran up
まだそこに着いたええ、私は走っていない
there yet yeah so people want to know
まだええ、人々 が知りたいと思っている
more details online I haven't got there
もっと詳しく オンラインで私 はそこ に いません
so for me because I'm a finisher yes I
だから私はフィニッシャーだから私のため に
want it to be finished before I give you
私があなたに与える前にそれが終わってほしい
the package yes but then people are like
パッケージは はいですが、その後は人 が似ています
well why didn't you tell me about this
あなたは この ことについて 私に 言わなかったのですか？
yeah like I could have helped get you to
ええ、私が あなたを助けてくれたように
where whether it was planning a vacation
どこで 休暇を計画していたの か
planning
プランニング
for groceries like how often do you get
あなたは どのくらいの 頻度で食べ物を食べるのですか
to the store and I'm messaging Karen do
店に私は カレンの メッセージを している
you need avocados do you know alamos how
あなたはアボカドが必要ですあなたは アラモス を知っていますか ？
many apples do we have rather than like
多くのリンゴは私たちが好きではなく持っています
okay let's sit down
さあ、座ってみましょう
but yeah the list rather than you know
しかし、あなたが知っているよりむしろリスト
and it happens at the grocery store all
それは食料雑貨 店ですべて 起こる
the time so often you go in and you know
とても頻繁にあなたが入ってあなたが知っている時間
you need eggs but then you're like oh
あなたは卵が必要ですが、あなたはああのようです
yeah but if I also need you also need
ええ、私も必要ならばあなたも必要です
and then you come home and somebody says
あなたは 家に帰って誰かが言う
to you did you get apples and you look
あなたはリンゴを手に入れましたか？
at them you're like why didn't you tell
あなたはなぜあなたに言っていないのですか？
me that you needed apples and you say
あなたがリンゴを必要とし、あなたが言うことを 私
wow I thought now this has not happened
うわー、私は今これが起こっていないと思った
here well I thought when you open in the
ここで私は あなたが
drawer and you saw there was no apples
引き出しとあなたはリンゴが見えなかった
you would figure that we needed apples
あなたは私たちがリンゴを必要とすることを 理解う
yeah right it's that whole inference
うん、 それは全体の推論です
thing rather than because communication
通信よりもむしろ事
actually needs to be worked on yeah it
実際に それを うまく処理する必要があります
is not the the workforce calls it a soft
労働者がそれをソフトと呼んでいるわけではありません
skill and it's one of the things that is
スキルと、それはある ものの一つです
like at the top of the hiring list yeah
雇用リストのトップのようにええ
so if you have good communication skills
もしあなた が良いコミュニケーションスキル を 持っているなら
then that is at the top of the list
それはリストの一番上にあります
people are looking to hire you but it's
人々 はあなたを雇うために探しています が、それは
something that you actually have to
あなたが実際に持っている何か
learn to do Wow I guess sometimes better
うわー、私は時々 、より良い 推測行うことを学びます
to over communicate something to tell
伝える ために何か を伝える
things two or three times it is to not
物事二、三回 、それは しないことです
say anything and it's it's so true when
何でも言えば
you think of people that you feel most
あなたは、あなたが最も感じている人々を考えます
comfortable with you know what's going
何が起こっているか知っている と快適 に
on with them because they told you so
彼らと 彼ら に はそうあなたに言った ので、
you don't feel like you're in the dark
あなたは 暗闇の中に いる ような 気がしない
and because when you know what's going
何が起こっ て いるのか を知って いる とき
on you feel safe you feel like there's a
あなたは安心しています。
plan I think you'll include it yes yeah
私はあなたが それをはい含まれている と思う計画
there's the confidence and a belonging
信頼と所属があります
yeah yes and and also when you are
はい、そしてまたあなたがいるとき
communicating with someone it does take
それが取る人とコミュニケーションする
that little piece of vulnerability so
脆弱性の その小さな 作品 そう
I'm sharing this with you what are you
私はこれをあなたと共有していますあなたは 何ですか
gonna do with it and so when it's
それと一緒にやっていくつもりです
reciprocated well it just reinforces
往復運動するだけで補強されます
that confidence that we're okay yeah you
私たちが大丈夫だ という自信
know and and this skill is so important
知っているとこのスキルはとても重要です
and it's so multi factorial in the way
それは途中で多階数である
that good communication skills come
その良いコミュニケーションスキルが来る
together that really to do it well is a
一緒に本当にそれをよくすることは
life hack because you can cut corners
あなたはコーナーを切ることができるので、人生のハック
and avoid problems and put up fires by
問題を避け、火災を
having quality communication
質の高いコミュニケーションを持つ
and there the book of Proverbs is full
箴言の本はいっぱいです
of these like gold nugget life hacks
これらの金のナゲットライフハックのような
that you can apply right now yes yes and
今すぐ 申し込む こと ができます はいはい
a life hack if you don't know what that
あなたが何を知っていなければ人生のハック
is is basically a tip that makes your
作る チップは基本的には、あなたの
life easier if and better and like one
もし簡単に、より良い とのような生活
of the things that that proverb says is
その 諺があると言う事の
the power of life and death is in the
生と 死 の力はです
tongue yeah right so that's a life hack
舌のええ、そう、それ は人生のハックだ
so when you think about how powerful
あなたが どれほど強力であるかを考えるとき
your tongue is and it can bring life or
あなたの舌があり、それは人生をもたらすことができますか
bring death and it's like oh I need to
死をもたらすとそれは私が必要と する ようなものです
be careful for with what I say and so
私が言うことと し、その ために注意してください
what we're going to do over you know a
私たちはあなたに何をしようとしていますか？
number of weeks a number of series maybe
おそらくシリーズの数の数
even throughout the next few months is
次の数ヶ月間でさえも
talk about certain life hacks from the
特定の人生のハックを話す
book of Proverbs that actually are going
実際に行っている諺の本
to help help your life because one of
あなたの 人生 を助けるため に
the things that people are often looking
人々がよく 見て いること
for is how do I make my life better
私の人生をより良く するにはどうしたらいいですか？
mm-hmm how do I get along with people
mm-hmmどうやったら 人 と付き合いますか
better how do I feel more confident in
どのように私はより自信を持って感じるのですか？
myself and I avoid conflict I Drive away
私と私は葛藤を避ける 私は離れて運転する
conflict how do I prove my relationship
競合がどのように私は 私の 関係を 証明します
with the Lord and one of the key things
主と鍵となるものの一つ
is so important to remember is that God
覚えておくことはとても重要です
can help us communicate well I I will
私たちは、 私は意志 よく 私を 伝えることができます
often say as a pastor dear Lord Jesus
多くの場合、牧師の愛する主イエス
please help my words through the power
私の言葉を 力で 助けて ください
of your Holy Spirit to communicate what
あなたの聖霊の何かを伝える
you want me to communicate but you can
あなたは私に 連絡してもらいたい
say that about your family about your
あなたの家族 について のあなたについてのことを言います
husband about your wife about your kids
あなたの子供 について あなたの妻 についての 夫
Lord would you guide and direct my work
主よ、私の仕事を指導して指揮しますか
so I'm communicating clearly to them
私は彼らに明確に伝えています
what is on my heart what I want to say
私が言いたい 私の心 に何であります
but also lord help me to hear what I
私の声を聞い て助けてくれます
need to hear and so when we talk about
聞く必要があるので話すとき
one of the best life hacks that you can
あなたができる最高の人生ハッキングの一つ
cultivate is listening skills hmm and
リスニングスキルが育っている
what we often say is well let me see if
私たちがよく言うことは 、
I understood you correctly so on that
私はあなたを正しく理解しました
note we're gonna pause
我々は一時停止するつもりであることに注意してください
welcome back right after these messages
これらの メッセージの直後にようこそ
[Music]
[音楽]
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
ThinkGeek ギアベストでお買い物をするかどうか
B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon or even
B＆H写真ビデオeBayまたはAmazonまたはさらに
if you want a free trial of audible
あなたが可聴の無料試用をしたい場合
you'll find the best deals and support
あなたは最高のお得な情報 とサポートを 見つけるでしょう
the shows we produce by simply visiting
単に訪問することによって私たちが作るショー
the shopping sites you already frequent
あなたが頻繁に行っているショッピングサイト
by using the links on our website visit
当社のウェブサイト訪問のリンクを使用して、
category 5 TV slash partners for the
カテゴリ5の TVスラッシュパートナー
full and ever-growing list and help us
完全かつ常に成長するリストと私たちを助ける
create more free content like this show
このショーのようにより多くの無料コンテンツを作成する
thank you for shopping with our partners
私たちのパートナーと 買い物をし て くれてありがとう
and thank you for watching
見て くれてありがとう
hey everyone welcome back thanks for
皆さん、 ありがとう
staying tuned to new every day we just
毎日新しいものに 気をつけて
want to thank our partners if you go to
あなたが行くなら 、私たちの パートナー に感謝し たい
our partners page on new every day dot
私たちのパートナーページは毎日新しいドットに
TV you can find all the organizations
テレビであなたはすべての組織を見つけることができます
and businesses who help support this
これ をサポートする企業
show and make it possible and I just
ショーとそれを可能にすると私はちょうど
want to let the viewers know that we are
視聴者に私たちがいることを知らせたい
under the umbrella of category 5 TV so
カテゴリ5テレビのような傘の下で
category 5 TV hosts new every day so
カテゴリ5つのTVホスト新しい毎日 そう
when you go to support the show you're
あなたがショーをサポートするために行くときは、 あなたは
hosting Robbie Ferguson our producer
私たちのプロデューサーである Robbie Ferguson
editor the guy who makes this all happen
エディター、これをすべて行う人
and that goes to support category 5
カテゴリ5 を サポートするようになる
which in turn trickles down and makes
今度はダウンしたたり落ちるとなります
new every day and a number of other
新しい毎日と他の多くの
shows possible yes so thank you for your
はい可能性を示すので 、あなたのためにあなたに 感謝
continued support so Jen I'm listening
私は聴いているので、継続的なサポート
what are we talking about we were
私たちは何を言っていた
talking about good communication skills
良い コミュニケーションスキル について話す
and how important it is to first of all
それがどれほど重要であるか
pray dear Lord Jesus help me to say what
愛する主イエス・キリストが私に
you want me to say yeah I pray that
あなたは私が祈って祈って欲しい
every morning help me to say what you
毎朝私はあなたのことを言うのに役立ちます
want me to say and help me to hear what
私が何かを聞くのを助けて
you want me to hear because so and we
あなたと私たちが聞いて欲しい
prayed this before we actually pushed
私たちが実際にプッシュする前にこれを祈った
record on the camera today I said Lord
今日私は 主 に言ったカメラの記録
we're still broken on the inside we
我々はまだ内部の 私たち に壊れています
operate out of like our sadness and our
私たちの悲しみ と私たち のように 外 の 動作
sore spots and so sometimes things come
痛みの斑点や時々ものが来る
out that we're like whoa where is that
私たちはどこにいるのか
coming from and to do this out really
これから本当にやって来る
you can't take it back in so it's like
あなたはそれを取り戻すことができないので、それは似ています
okay would you and and proverbs does say
あなたと諺は言うでしょうか？
that I don't know where it's it's found
それがどこにあるのかわからない
right now but it says or could be Psalms
今は言うが、それは詩篇であるかもしれない
who says that you put a guard on my
あなたは私に
mouth
口
and you know people often make say the
あなたは、人々はしばしば言う作る知っています
phrase God gave us two ears and one
フレーズ 神は私たちに2つの耳 と 1 つを与えました
mouth so that we can listen twice as
私たちは 2度 聞くことができます
much as we speak right well James says
ジェームスは言う
that we should be quick to listen slow
私たちは遅く聞こえるはずです
to speak and slow to become angry and I
話すことと遅く怒るし、I
think there's great wisdom in that
偉大な知恵が、 その 中にあると思います
there's an there's like an old Indian
古いインド人のようなものがあります
proverb that says he who knows does not
知っている人が言っていることわざ
speak he who speaks does not know yes
話す彼は言う
and sometimes that is true yes and so
そして時にはそれは本当にそうです。
one of the verses is so important is
詩の一つがとても重要です
that when we fail to listen we actually
我々は 実際に 我々を聞くために 失敗した場合
fall we can fall into a ditch like we
我々は我々のような溝 に 落ちることができる落ちます
just get ourselves into so much trouble
そんなに大きなトラブルに陥る
yeah when we fail to listen yeah and so
ええ 、私たちは そうええ 聞くために 失敗 し たとき
one of the best things that you can do
あなたができる最高のものの一つ
for a listening goes like this you're
聞い てみると、これはあなたのようになります
good at that but just to be quiet just
それだけではなく、ちょうど静か になる
to be quiet yeah and listen and so often
静かなええ と聞く と頻繁に
you want to jump in to somebody else's
あなたは他の誰かに飛び込みたい
sentence before they've even finished it
彼らも それを 終えた前の文
looks like this yeah it's so like even
この ように見えます
yeah I think that if you so if you
ええ、私は 考えている場合 であれば そう します
actually then he who answers before
実際 に彼は前に答えた
listening that is his falling and his
それを 聞いては、 彼は落下し、彼のさ
shame okay did you see how awkward that
恥ずかしがり屋あなたはそれがいかに厄介かを見たか？
is I know we've all done that before if
それ以前に私たちがやったことは分かっていますか？
you ever talk to someone and they're
あなたは誰か と話したことが あります
like and they're like ready to think of
などが挙げられ、これらは考えるために準備が似ています
the next thing that they want to say and
彼ら が言い たい 次の こと
they haven't actually heard so you don't
彼らは実際に聞いたことがないので、あなたはしません
feel valued and they're missing out on
価値があると感じていて 、彼らは欠けている
the opportunity to learn from you yes
あなたから学ぶ機会
because they haven't heard you through
彼ら はあなたを聞い て いない ので
all the way to the end yeah they've
彼らが終わったええ 、終わりまでのすべての道
already formulated that like you said
すでにあなたが言ったように
what they're already going to say but
彼らはすでに言おうとしているが、
they haven't actually finished listening
彼らは実際に聞いて終わっていない
to what you're going to say yeah so I
あなたは 私が そう 言おうと しているものに
think there's a lot of wisdom in that
そこにはたくさんの知恵があると思う
and that's just like one pearl one
それは まるで真珠のようなものです
nugget from the book of Proverbs that if
諺の本のナゲット
you answer before listening it's to your
それを聞く前にあなたは答えます
own folly and shame and that's something
自分の愚かさと恥とは何か
good to remember as we talk and interact
私たちが話して交流 するときに 覚えておくと良い
with people so Jen we have to wrap up
人々と一緒に私たちは包み込む必要があります
already but there are so many other good
すでに他の良いものがたくさんある
life hacks coming your way I'm really
あなたのやり方で生きているハック私は本当に
looking forward to this
これを楽しみにして
session seasons episodes yeah talking
セッションシーズンエピソード 喋る
talking with you listening what are you
あなたが 何であるかを 聞いてと話
pray and I'll listen well I'm gonna pray
祈って、私は よく 聞く よ私は祈るつもりだ
because one of the things that we often
私たちがよく使うことの1つ
hear time and time again is nobody
もう一度時間と時間を聞く
listens so we're gonna pray you're gonna
私たちはあなたが祈るつもりなので耳を傾ける
be a good listener this week so dear
今週はとてもいいリスナーになれ
Lord Jesus help us to listen well this
主イエスは、 私たちはよくこのことを聞くために役立ちます
week help us not to focus on what the
週に集中し ないでください。
things that we want to say to be
我々が言いたいこと
understood but help us to listen so we
理解したが、私たちは私 たちを 聞くために役立ちます
can understand others we ask this in
私たちがこれを求めて いる他の人 を理解する
your name amen thank you so much for
あなたの名前は 非常にありがとう
tuning in and we're going to see you
チューニングインして、あなたに会いに行きます
back here same time same place and we're
同じ場所で同じ場所に戻ってきて
gonna keep this conversation going so
つもりは そう だろう、この会話を続けます
have a great week cheers there Jen catch
すばらしい 週があります。
a new episode of new every day every
新しい毎日の新しいエピソード
Friday morning at new every day dot TV
金曜日の朝、新しい 毎日の ドット テレビ
we're also on Kody Roku Plex YouTube and
私たちはKody Roku PlexのYouTubeと
Facebook or if you're in Southern
Facebook またはあなたが南部にいれば
California tune in every Sunday morning
毎週日曜日に カリフォルニア州で 調整する
at 6:30 Pacific on channel 33 television
チャンネル33の6:30太平洋でテレビ
for the high desert
高い砂漠のために